EASY_QUESTIONS = [{"question": "What is the value of x in: 2x + 3 = 9", "answers": ["5", "1", "3", "8"], "correct": 2},
                  {"question": "How many sides does a decagon have?", "answers": ["5", "10", "7", "4"], "correct": 1},
                  {"question": "What's the square root of 81?" , "answers": ["9", "3", "81", "18"] , "correct": 0},
                  {"question": "What is the 20% of 2500?", "answers": ["25", "75", "125", "500"], "correct": 3},
                  {"question": "What is the value of 13^2?", "answers": ["121", "100", "196", "169"], "correct": 3},
                  {"question": "What is the perimeter of a square with a 5cm side?", "answers": ["10", "20", "25", "15"], "correct": 1},
                  {"question": "If x = 3, y = 2, what's the value of 2x + 3y?", "answers": ["8", "14", "12", "11"] , "correct": 2},
                  {"question": "What is the square root of 8100?", "answers": ["81", "30", "60", "90"] , "correct": 3},
                  {"question": "What's the next number of the sequence. 2, 4, 8, 16,___", "answers": ["26", "24", "32", "36"] , "correct": 2},
                  {"question": "What's the value of 4!?", "answers": ["12", "24", "120", "6"] , "correct": 1}]

MEDIUM_QUESTIONS = [{"question": "What is the value of x in the equation 2x + 5 = 15?", "answers": ["4", "6", "5", "3"], "correct": 2},
                    {"question": "What is 15×12?", "answers": ["180", "200", "150", "165"], "correct": 0},
                    {"question": "What is the square root of 256?", "answers": ["14", "16", "18", "20"], "correct": 1},
                    {"question": "What is the area of a triangle with a base of 10 and a height of 8?", "answers": ["50", "40", "80", "30"], "correct": 1},
                    {"question": "If a car travels 120 km in 2 hours, what is its average speed?", "answers": ["50 km/h", "70 km/h", "60 km/h", "80 km/h"], "correct": 2},
                    {"question": "What is the value of 15×7−18?", "answers": ["96", "105", "87", "93"], "correct": 2},
                    {"question": "Solve for x: 4x+9=25", "answers": ["x = 3", "x = 4", "x = 5", "x = 6"], "correct": 1},
                    {"question": "What is the area of a triangle with a base of 8 units and height of 12 units?", "answers": ["48", "50", "56", "60"], "correct": 0},
                    {"question": "What is the value of 24/6 + 8 · 2?", "answers": ["24", "20", "28", "30"], "correct": 1},
                    {"question": "Simplify 5(3x−2)= 4x+1", "answers": ["x = 3", "x = 4", "x = 1", "x = 2"], "correct": 2}]



















